Wow! That's great!
Good morning.
Spring Facial Broadcast
Look.
Ouch.
Ahh.
Look, oh my gosh, today we are at Yokohama Buntai for Haru Tokimeki Haru no Hinarebutai 2024. The arena was newly opened in April, so the backstage is very beautiful!
Look at that, my eyes are moving!
I'm so hungry!
Today we have a live band.
We're going to play some spring songs, too.
Let's go for another day!
I went to a spa yesterday.
I went to a spa yesterday to detoxify my body.
I went to the spa yesterday to detoxify my body, and I bought a bedtime gift for everyone there.
I'll give them to you later.
Is she going to be okay?
I'm going to be made into the most adorable idol ever.
Bye-bye.
Pandaman?
Moon of Yokohama
I bought pickled plums for everyone.
I'll put in a picture of you like a grandma!
A very small cake!
These cakes are full of pictures!
Here is the lineup
Honey koume (small plums)
The one that's not a little plum with honey koume and the one that's not a little plum with honey ume and the one that's not a little plum
Looks delicious!
Tasty ume that I want to eat
I'm happy with the tasty looking pickled plums
Order the salt content
I'll get it.
Green
I see Mitsuko tastes okay? I'm taking pictures.
It tastes a little like meat.
Strawberry.
What color is green?
Wait a minute.
What's this? It's pretty.
Pretty that way!
A shark?
It's a shark!
What does it taste like?
It tastes like peaches.
It's so cold!
There are so many kinds today.
Is that right? It came out this time.
No, it's not.
I once told an artist...
The artist's favorite candy.
My favorite candy.
Oh, it's true.
I ate about 3 Jillian's when we were doing the side split.
What's the matter, it tastes different.
It was different from the last time I wrote about it.
Oh, yeah.
Yay.
There's shark.
Is it matcha green tea?
It looks like matcha.
What is it?
Is it the best?
Peach? Peach?
Peach? Peaches.
The other day, Jillia said she was going to buy them with money.
I ate them that night. How many did you eat?
Five.
Four.
My back hurts.
My back hurts, but I'm already scared... 4... I don't know if they taste so good or not...
Four! They were so good!
Caramel, chocolate, Earl Grey and
Macho.
They were delicious?
Crunchy! It tasted so good.
Bento's here, too.
Oh, but I like to wash the crunchy isdos.
Oh, it's delicious.
It's so good!
It was delicious.
And fresh ponder.
Nama ponder?
Mochi's new one.
Oh, the new one?
I want some.
I'll try it.
I'm going to try it.
I was wondering.
You're right, there's not a lot of this music.
I don't think so.
Shaggy, shaggy, shaggy.
Hey, let's put on some makeup first.
I love Chinatown.
Oh, here we are.
It's coming off.
Vegetables.
What's with the change of location?
They moved this one up.
What should we eat?
I don't know.
I can't find any chocolate.
I'm going to buy some more of that chocolate that I like to wrap up in plastic wrap and take home.
I'd love to wrap it up and take it home.
I've already decided on number one.
Oh, wait.
I'll try this one too.
Okay.
This one.
Oh!
Chocolate is good, right?
I'm going to make some chocolate bread tomorrow.
I'll probably take him home tomorrow.
I'm done with Choco and I'm going home.
I can take him home today.
I can take him home today too.
This morning.
I had this big autumn sweet potato.
It was a big one this morning
Yes
Yes.
There was a toy that came and was surprisingly soft
Here's a toy.
Thank you. Thank you.
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Oh, that's cute.
It's cute.
Shark.
Long time no see.
What's a mong man?
I'll have strawberries or chocolate later for dessert.
What do you want now? I'll check the song.
Or you can have a bun.
Shark's fin.
What does it feel like? What kind of shark's fin is that?
Shall we check? Hito-chan will eat pork now.
Machacha and Haru will eat ramen now.
When I got in the car this morning, I wondered why you had this.
Ah! Shotty!
Sking.
Gengen.
I could eat around here forever.
Good morning to you!
Good morning to you, please watch the various videos, good morning, good morning, please...
Good morning, everyone!
You're so cute!
They have cute faces.
It's too cute.
I'm sure you'll be able to confirm it, right?
Looks like a good song confirmation.
Here's a specially selected YouTube.
Oh, it's YouTube.
I'll do my best.
Here's Mizuki King and Yasshi from the Special Selection band!
They're so cute!
Oh, I got it!
Oh, it's Tamagodou pudding!
Oh, it's so cute!
I heard it's for separating the yolk from the egg yolk.
Interesting!
Pudding on egg yolk... interesting!
Pudding is coming!
Oh, is he waiting already?
I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting!
Chicks, rehearsal's over.
What's next?
You've been eating bento lately.
Yes, I have.
Soybeans and kanpyo.
We always have these, don't we?
Bon appétit.
Oh, it comes in so many flavors.
Yes, it's so good!
What is it?
What is it? - me pudding!
This is pudding too!
me our campion rolls!
Oh, there it is again! It's the sun!
Yay!
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Nice to meet you.
Rambollan
Koller
Strawberry
Collett-Roe.
Colletro Colletro Strawberry beer? Yes, it is.
I am pink. I, potato. Mmm.
me
Don't be bothered by the sun.
What's wrong with you?
I'll have strawberry milk macaroon.
I'll have my lunch.
Bon appétit!
Look at this
Hiramagami.
Isn't it amazing?
You're all frozen up.
It's embarrassing.
But I'm 80% so far.
I've been told that's 80%.
Today... the first dress is a really cute rock 'n' roll outfit.
Is that leather?
It's a really thick, sweat-proof fabric.
It's also very thick with long sleeves.
The stage itself was thick today.
I'm sure I'm going to sweat a lot.
It's so beautiful!
Chichi Chichiro!
Then I'd like to change.
There? So beautiful!
I'll be right back.
The show's over... and we've been married for hours.
The power of love...
The power of love has degenerated.
I'm in a bit of trouble.
I don't know what to do.
We're kind of stuck together.
It's sticking to me
Oh, it's stuck!
Aki-chan, Aki-chan
We rock!
We rock
I found something.
Heplin, Heplin fits Heplin.
That's about 10 million.
Yeah, someone's written all over it.
Our Queasy is awesome.
Queasy.
Who's that 10 million or so?
Everybody.
All right.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Ta-da!
Charbroughs Charbrothers.
My name is Charbrough Rose.
These are my Charbroze brand clothes.
It's easy to wear!
Pudding pudding I was saying earlier.
I'm allowed to eat the pudding so it cools down.
This is how I make the cream.
I wrote lines and names.
I'm going to put a raw egg out here on the lid.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Somebody help me, wait, I'll clean it up later, I'll clean it up later
I'll clean it up later. I'm sorry, I'll clean it up later! I'll clean it up later! I'll clean it up later! I'm sorry! I'll clean it up later!
Oh, this is hard!
I ended up putting the white meat on too.
I don't know what's going on, but...
I don't know what it is, but I don't know what it is.
I'm going to put away the white meat.
Don't tell anyone that I did this, but I don't seem to need the white meat.
Like this, like this.
I'm going to caramelize it.
I did it again!
Like this... like this...
And so on...
The pudding is done!
It's done!
I'm going to eat it now!
Oh no!
It's spilling. I'll take one.
Oh, no, I'll wipe it off.
Oh, it's so good!
It's so good!
I can go for about five.
Okay, let's wipe it up.
Let's wipe it with water.
My hands are stiff!
It was a bit of a flurry, but the pudding is finished, so I'm taking it home with me. Bye bye.
Here comes the pudding's senior.
Pudding's senpai.
Forget it. It's too much work.
Forget it.
I put only the yolk of the egg on that pudding, but I have to serve something.
You should put out something that's going to be big like this.
Did you use this?
Yes, I did.
But, you know, just put the yolk on it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Just put the yolk on top.
Let me see.
I'll take it out.
Ah, it's G-Chiro!
I'm going to eat my favorite "giichiro"!
You're good!
I switched Puddin' Puddin' here.
Kamuli!
I didn't find it.
Good job!
You're so different from Junior.
It's good, right? I've never seen this before.
I've never seen it before.
It's perfect.
Yay. It's perfect.
The cream, it's so good, this is so good.
I can go for about 5 more.
Look, avocado cheese crackers.
Looks so good.
What did I just say?
You had a lot of them, didn't you? I ate them.
What were they?
I don't know.
It was delicious.
Well, I'll have some of that.
I have a lot of lunches, so I'll take one.
Second one.
Let's get more aggressive, let's get more aggressive, let's get more aggressive!
The most powerful live performance is...
The six of us, and the publicity staff...
And with everyone's voice...
I think it's the strongest live performance.
That's why we will definitely come back to this big, big Saitama Super Arena.
I want to come back to this big Saitama Super Arena with all of us.
It may be a very big dream.
But if we all do our best to pursue our dreams together
I'm sure we can make it come true.
Let's make such a big dream come true together.
Let's become a more powerful Tokimeki Sengen Club!
Let's become the most powerful Tokimeki Sentanbu and I want to give it to you, so let's go wherever you want to go and see the unknown scenery that is still in front of us
Goodbye goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart
Paint a piece of the future on the canvas of my broken heart
They guide me through the bad times I've been going through
And it's leading me on.
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears, and when I'm lost, I'll remember it right away
When it's raining, I'll try to smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets sparkle
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools, making rainbow sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a feather
Tears are making me do it
I'll wear a rainbow dress la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la